19th-20th Century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
19th-20th century North American Architecture Lantern Slide Collection
1900-1960
VRC 2006
Yale University Arts Library
51
153 boxes
Collection consists of black and white glass lantern slides of Canadian and U.S. architecture to the mid-twentieth century.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Collection consists of black and white glass lantern slides of Canadian and U.S. architecture to the mid-twentieth century.
Arrangement
Arranged by country. Further sub-divided by city or other location and building type or name.
Architecture -- Canada -- 19th century; Architecture -- Canada -- 20th Century; Architecture -- United States -- History -- 19th century; Architecture -- United States -- History -- 20th Century; Lantern slides; Slides; Reproductions
- United States (Box 1)
  - General (Box 1)
    - Various (Box 1)
    - Ports (Box 1)
    - Log Cabins (Box 1)
    - Sod Houses (Box 1)
    - Super graphics (Box 1)
  - Landscaping (Box 1)
  - Cartoons (Box 1)
    - Addams Cartoons (Box 1)
    - Osborn Cartoons (Box 1)
    - Petty Cartoons (Box 1)
  - Magazines & Books (Box 1)
  - Airports (Box 1)
  - Churches (Box 1)
  - Expositions (Box 1)
  - Gardens (Box 1)
  - Highways/Streets (Box 1–2)
  - Hospitals (Box 2)
  - Houses (Box 2)
    - Various (Box 2)
    - Plans/Elevations (Box 2)
    - Exterior (Box 2–3)
    - 1961 Hallmark House (Box 3)
  - Housing (Box 3)
  - Industrial Buildings (Box 3)
  - Interiors (Box 3)
    - Bathrooms (Box 3)
    - Bedrooms (Box 3–4)
    - Dinning Rooms (Box 4)
    - Dressing Rooms (Box 4)
    - Kitchens (Box 4)
    - Living Rooms (Box 4)
    - Offices (Box 4)
    - Porches & Patios (Box 4)
  - Interiors: Exhibits (Box 4)
    - Architect & the Industrial Arts 1929 (Box 4)
  - Interiors: Museum Rooms (Box 4)
    - Boston Museum: American Wing (Box 4)
    - Metropolitan Museum American wing (Box 4–5)
    - Smithsonian Institution (Box 5)
  - Mobile Homes (Box 5)
  - Parks & Traffic (Box 5)
  - Parks & Park Building (Box 5)
  - Planning (Box 5)
  - Communication Building (Box 5)
  - Neighborhood Units (Box 5–6)
  - Schools (Box 6)
  - Architects (Box 6)
    - Various (Box 6)
    - Adams, Thomas (Box 6)
    - Arnot (Box 6)
    - Austin, Henry, 1804-1891 (Box 6)
    - Baum, Dwight J. (Box 6)
    - Bell, William (Box 6)
    - Benjamin, Asher (Box 6)
    - Bennett, Richard (Box 6)
    - Bickdell (Box 6)
    - Blossom, Alfred (Box 6)
    - Born, Ernest (Box 6)
    - Bradles, N.J. (Box 6)
    - Bragdon, Claude (Box 7)
    - Brooks, S.H. (Box 7)
    - Buffington, Leroy (Box 7)
    - Bulfinch, Charles (Box 7)
    - Butterfield, W.H. (Box 7)
    - Byrne, Barry (Box 7)
    - Cady, J.C. (Box 7)
    - Carnegie Corporation of N.Y. (Box 7)
    - Carrere (Box 7)
    - Caudill (Box 7)
    - Christ-Janer, Victor (Box 7)
    - Clarke, Gilbert (Box 7)
    - Cleaveland (Box 7)
    - Cummings, G.P. (Box 7)
    - Davis, Alexander Jackson, 1803-1892 (Box 7)
    - Dirlan, A.A. (Box 7)
    - Downing, Andrew Jackson, 1815-1852 (Box 7–8)
    - Emerson, William Ralph (Box 8)
    - Eyre, Wilson, 1858-1944 (Box 8)
    - Ferriss, Hugh, 1889-1962 (Box 8)
    - Franzen, Ulrich (Box 8)
    - Fuller, Buckminster, 1895-1983 (Box 8)
    - Gardner, E.C. (Box 8)
    - Geddes, Robert (Box 8)
    - Geddes Norman Del (Box 8)
    - Giurgola, R. & Association (Box 8)
    - Goldsmith Jonathan (Box 8)
    - Greene, Charles & Henry (Box 8)
    - Gutterson, Henry (Box 8)
    - Harkness, John C. (Box 8)
    - Harrinson, Peter (Box 8)
    - Hastings (Box 8)
    - Havilland, John (Box 8)
    - Hicks, Granville (Box 9)
    - Holly, Henry Hudson (Box 9)
    - Hopkins, John H. (Box 9)
    - Howe, George (Box 9)
    - Howe, Lescaze (Box 9)
    - Hurd (Box 9)
    - Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826 (Box 9)
    - Johansen, John McLane, 1916- (Box 9)
    - Johnson, Philip Cortelyou, 1906-2005 (Box 9)
    - Kahn, Louis I., 1901-1974 (Box 9)
    - Hicks, Granville (Box 9)
    - Holly, Henry Hudson (Box 9)
    - Hopkins, John H. (Box 9)
    - Howe, George (Box 9)
    - Howe, Lescaze (Box 9)
    - Hurd (Box 9)
    - Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826 (Box 9)
    - Johansen, John McLane, 1916- (Box 9)
    - Johansen, John McLane, 1916- (Box 9)
    - Johansen, John McLane, 1916- (Box 9)
    - Kiesler, Frederick (Box 10)
    - Kirby, J.H. (Box 10)
    - Lafaver, Minard, 1798-1854 (Box 10)
    - Lamantia, James (Box 10)
    - Lamb, Theodore (Box 10)
    - Latrobe, Benjamin Henry, 1764-1820 (Box 10)
    - Lay, Charles (Box 10)
    - McKim, Charles (Box 10)
    - McIntire, Samuel (Box 10)
    - Mills, Robert (Box 10)
    - Molnar, Farkas (Box 10)
    - Nalle, Eugene (Box 10)
    - Nelson, Paul (Box 10)
    - Neutra, Richard (Box 10)
    - Nowicki, Matthew, 1910-1950 (Box 10)
    - Palliser, Geo-A. (Box 11)
    - Peabody (Box 11)
    - Peck, Bradford (Box 11)
    - Pei, I.M. & Associates (Box 11)
    - Polk, Willis (Box 11)
    - Potter, E.T. (Box 11)
    - Poulson, Nils (Box 11)
    - Price, Bruce (Box 11)
    - Primatt, Stephen (Box 11)
    - Ranlett, W.H. (Box 11)
    - Raymond, Antonin (Box 11)
    - Riddell, John (Box 11)
    - Richt, John (Box 11)
    - Scott, Frank (Box 11)
    - Sixwiekher, Paul (Box 11)
    - Sidney, J.C. (Box 12)
    - Skillings & Flint (Box 12)
    - Sloan, Samuel (Box 12)
    - Smith, Henry (Box 12)
    - Solery, Paolo (Box 12)
    - Stickley, Gustave (Box 12)
    - Stone, Edward Durrell, 1902-1978 (Box 12)
    - Strickland, William, 1787-1854 (Box 12)
    - Sullivan, Louis, 1856-1924 (Box 12)
    - Thorp, A.H. (Box 12)
    - Tuttle (Box 12)
    - Town, Ithiel (Box 12)
    - Urban (Box 12)
    - Valk, L.B. (Box 12)
    - Vaux, Calvert (Box 12)
    - Venturi, Robert, 1925 (Box 12)
      - Various (Box 12)
      - Frug House Project (Box 13)
      - Millard Meiss House Project (Box 13)
      - Priceton Memorial Park Project (Box 13)
      - Three Buildings Project, North Canton, OH (Box 13)
    - Wagner, Martin (Box 13)
    - Walker, Bruce (Box 13)
    - Wheeler, Gervase (Box 13)
    - White, Stanford (Box 13)
    - Winsor, Justin (Box 13)
    - Wither (Box 13)
    - Wood, William (Box 13)
    - Woodsend, H.E. (Box 13)
    - Woodward, George (Box 13)
    - Woollett (Box 13)
    - Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959 (Box 13)
      - Various (Box 13)
      - American System Ready-Cut Bungalow (Box 14)
      - Barnsdall Theaters (Box 14)
      - Blockfor C.E. Roberts (Box 14)
      - Broadacre City (Box 14)
      - Davidson Sheet, Steel Farms Units (Box 14)
      - Doheny Ranch (Box 14)
      - Fireproof House (Box 14)
      - Hotel for Lacey (Box 14)
      - Hotel for Lacey (Box 14)
      - Laketahoe Colony (Box 14)
      - Larkinco work-men's Houses (Box 14)
      - Larkinco work-men's Houses (Box 14)
      - Life House, 1938 (Box 14)
      - W. MacArthur House (Box 14)
      - H. McCormick House (Box 14)
      - S. Marcus House (Box 14)
      - National Life Insurance Company (Box 14)
      - Elizabeth Nobel Apartment House (Box 14)
      - Press Building (Box 14)
      - Sports Club/Huntington Hartford (Box 15)
      - S. Mark's Tower (Box 15)
      - San Marcos-In-The Desert, AZ (Box 15)
      - Wright's Studio Home Project (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous Cities (Box 15)
    - Abo, NM (Box 15)
    - Acoma, NM (Box 15)
    - Adam Through- Good House (Box 15)
    - Adams, MN (Box 15)
    - Ajo, AZ (Box 15)
    - Akron, OH (Box 15)
    - Addison, VT (Box 15)
    - Albany, NY (Box 15)
      - Banks (Box 15)
      - Government Buildings (Box 15)
        - City Hall, 1882 (Box 15)
        - State Capitol (Box 15)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 15)
        - Sill House (Box 15)
      - Schools (Box 15)
    - Alexandria, VA (Box 16)
      - Various (Box 16)
      - Christ Church (Box 16)
    - Algona, IA (Box 16)
    - Alhambra, CA (Box 16)
    - Allengheny, PA (Box 16)
    - Allentown, PA (Box 16)
    - Altadena, CA (Box 16)
    - Amagansett, NY (Box 16)
    - Ambler, PA (Box 16)
    - Amesbury, MA (Box 16)
    - Amherst, MA (Box 16)
    - Amherst, NH (Box 16)
    - Andalusia, PA (Box 16)
    - Andover, MA (Box 16)
    - Angelica, NY (Box 16)
    - Annandale-on- Hudson, NY (Box 16)
    - Annapolis, MD (Box 16)
      - State Capitol (Box 16)
      - Houses (Box 16)
        - Various (Box 16)
        - Brice House (Box 16)
        - Hammond-Hardwood House (Box 16)
        - Carvel House (Box 16)
        - Chase House (Box 16)
        - Scott House (Box 17)
      - Schools (Box 17)
        - St. John's College (Box 17)
    - Ann Arbor, MI (Box 17)
    - Annisquam, MA (Box 17)
    - Ansonia, CT (Box 17)
    - Ardmore, PA (Box 17)
    - Arlington, MA (Box 17)
    - Arlington, VA (Box 17)
    - Asheville, NC (Box 17)
    - Ashby, MA (Box 17)
    - Athens, GA (Box 17)
    - Atlanta, GA (Box 17)
    - Atlantic City, NJ (Box 18)
    - Auburn, NY (Box 18)
    - Auburndale, MA (Box 18)
    - Audubon, PA (Box 18)
    - Augusta, GA (Box 18)
    - Augusta, ME (Box 18)
    - Aurora, IL (Box 18)
      - Various (Box 18)
      - Banks (Box 18)
    - Austin, TX (Box 18)
    - Avon Village, TX (Box 18)
    - Avon, CT (Box 18)
    - Baja California (Box 18)
    - Bains (Box 18)
    - Bakersfield, CA (Box 18)
    - Baldwin, NY (Box 18)
    - Baltimore, MD (Box 18)
      - Various (Box 18)
      - Banks (Box 18)
      - Churches (Box 18)
        - Various (Box 18)
        - Boundary (Box 18)
        - Cathedral (Box 18)
        - First Baptist (Box 18)
        - First Presbyterian (Box 18)
        - Chapel (Box 18)
        - Green Mount Cemetery (Box 18)
        - Lafayette (Box 18)
        - Otterbein Church (Box 18)
        - S. Mary's Seminary Church (Box 18)
        - S. Paul's (Box 18)
      - Government Buildings (Box 18)
      - Houses (Box 18)
        - Various (Box 18)
        - Glen Ellen (Box 19)
        - Home Wood Villa (Box 19)
          - Exterior (Box 19)
          - Interior (Box 19)
      - Libraries (Box 19)
      - Monuments (Box 19)
      - Museums (Box 19)
        - Peabody Institution (Box 19)
        - Peale's Baltimore Museum (Box 19)
        - Walters Art Gallery (Box 19)
      - Office Buildings (Box 19)
      - Prisons (Box 19)
      - Schools (Box 19)
      - Stations (Box 19)
      - Stores (Box 19)
    - Bangor, ME (Box 19)
    - Bar Harbor, ME (Box 19)
    - Barryntown, NY (Box 20)
    - Bath, ME (Box 20)
    - Baton Rouge, LA (Box 20)
      - Government Buildings (Box 20)
      - Houses (Box 20)
    - Bar Harbor, TX (Box 20)
    - Beacon, NY (Box 20)
    - Bear Run, PA (Box 20)
    - Beaufort, SC (Box 20)
    - Bedford, PA (Box 20)
    - Bel Air, CA (Box 20)
    - Belfast, ME (Box 20)
    - Belleville, NY (Box 20)
    - Bellemawr, NJ (Box 20)
    - Bellows Falls, UT (Box 20)
    - Belmont, CA (Box 20)
    - Belmont, MA (Box 20)
      - Koch House (Box 20)
    - Benicia, CA (Box 20)
    - Bennington, VT (Box 20)
    - Berkeley, CA (Box 20)
      - Churches (Box 20–21)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 21)
        - Various (Box 21)
        - Benner House (Box 21)
        - Colby House (Box 21)
        - Hillside House (Box 21)
        - Jensen House (Box 21)
        - Kennedy House (Box 21)
        - Lamson House (Box 21)
        - Weston Havens House (Box 21)
          - Exterior (Box 21)
          - Interior (Box 21)
      - Schools (Box 21)
    - Berlin, CT (Box 21)
    - Berlin, MA (Box 21)
    - Bethany, CT (Box 21)
    - Bethlehem, PA (Box 21)
    - Bethel, CT (Box 21)
    - Beverly, MA (Box 21)
    - Beverley Hills, CA (Box 21)
    - Biloxi, MS (Box 21)
    - Birmingham, MI (Box 21)
    - Bismarck, ND (Box 21)
    - Bloomfield Hills, MI (Box 22)
      - Houses (Box 22)
      - Schools (Box 22)
        - GranBrook (Box 22)
        - Kingwood (Box 22)
    - Boise, Idaho (Box 22)
    - Boston, MA (Box 22)
      - General (Box 22)
      - Planning (Box 22)
      - Banks (Box 22)
      - Churches (Box 22)
        - Various (Box 22)
        - Central Congregational Church (Box 23)
        - Charles St. Church (Box 23)
        - Christian Science (Box 23)
        - Federal St. Church (Box 23)
        - King's Chapel (Box 23)
        - New South Church (Box 23)
        - Old North Church (Box 23)
        - Old South Church (Box 23)
        - Park St. Church (Box 23)
        - S. Paul's Cathedral (Box 23)
        - Trinity Church (Box 23)
      - Clubs (Box 23)
        - Algoquin Club (Box 23)
      - Government Buildings (Box 23)
        - Various (Box 23)
        - City Hall, 1862 (Box 23)
        - City Hall, 1963 (Box 23)
        - Competition City Hall, 1960-1962 (Box 23–24)
        - Court House (Box 24)
        - Customs House (Box 24)
        - Old State House (Box 24)
        - Post Office (Box 24)
        - State House (Box 24)
        - State Services Center, 1963 (Box 24)
        - Town House (Box 24)
      - Hospitals (Box 24)
      - Hotels (Box 24)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 24)
        - Various (Box 24)
        - Chase House (Box 24)
        - Drayton House (Box 24)
        - Franklin Crescent House (Box 24)
        - Hancock House (Box 24)
        - Harrison Gray Otis House (Box 24)
        - Harrison Gray Otis House #2 (Box 24)
        - Harrison Gray Otis House #3 (Box 24)
        - Mt. Vernon St. Houses (Box 24)
        - Park St. Houses (Box 24)
        - Paul Revere House (Box 24)
        - Sears House (Box 24)
        - South Boston Houses (Box 25)
      - Libraries (Box 25)
        - Atheneum (Box 25)
        - Boston Public Library (Box 25)
      - Markets (Box 25)
        - Boylston (Box 25)
        - Quincy (Box 25)
      - Monuments (Box 25)
      - Museums (Box 25)
        - Gardner Museum (Box 25)
        - Museum of Fine Arts (Box 25)
      - Office Buildings (Box 25)
        - Back Bay Areas (Box 25)
        - Blue Cross Building (Box 25)
        - Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Box 25)
      - Parks (Box 25)
      - Stations (Box 25)
        - North Station (Box 25)
        - Park St. Station (Box 25)
        - South Station (Box 25)
      - Schools (Box 26)
      - Squares (Box 26)
      - Stores (Box 26)
        - Ames (Box 26)
        - India Wharf (Box 26)
      - Theaters (Box 26)
      - Warehouses (Box 26)
    - Boulder, CO (Box 26)
    - Boulder, NV (Box 26)
    - Boxford, MA (Box 26)
      - Saw, Grist & Knife Mill Group (Box 26)
    - Brentwood, CA (Box 26)
    - Branford, CT (Box 26)
    - Bridgeport, CT (Box 26)
      - Various (Box 26)
      - Harral House (Box 26)
    - Bristol, PA (Box 26)
    - Bristol, RI (Box 26)
    - Broad Creek, MD (Box 26)
    - Bronx, NY (Box 27)
    - Bronxville, NY (Box 27)
    - Brookline, MA (Box 27)
    - Brooklyn, CT (Box 27)
    - Brooklyn, NY (Box 27)
      - Banks (Box 27)
      - Cemeteries (Box 27)
      - Churches (Box 27)
      - Government Buildings (Box 27)
      - Hospitals (Box 27)
      - Hotels (Box 27)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 27)
      - Housing (Box 27)
        - Clinton Hill Apartments (Box 27)
        - Riverside Buildings (Box 27)
        - Williamsburg Buildings (Box 27)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 27)
      - Museums (Box 27)
      - Office Buildings (Box 28)
      - Parkways (Box 28)
      - Schools (Box 28)
      - Stores (Box 28)
      - Theaters (Box 28)
    - Brookville, NY (Box 28)
    - Brunswick, ME (Box 28)
      - Churches (Box 28)
      - Houses (Box 28)
    - Bryn Mawr, PA (Box 28)
    - Buffalo, NY (Box 28)
      - Airports (Box 28)
      - Banks (Box 28)
      - Churches (Box 28)
      - Clubs (Box 28)
      - Exhibitions (Box 28)
        - Buffalo Exposition, 1901 (Box 28)
      - Government Buildings (Box 28)
      - Hotels (Box 28)
      - Houses (Box 28)
        - Various (Box 28)
        - Heat House (Box 28)
        - Martin House (Box 28)
        - Metcalf House (Box 28)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 28)
      - Museums (Box 28)
      - Office Buildings (Box 28)
        - Guaranty Building (Box 28)
        - Larkin Soap Co. Building (Box 28)
      - Stations (Box 28)
    - Burlington, NJ (Box 28)
    - Burlington, VT (Box 28)
    - Cahokia, IL (Box 28)
    - California (Box 28)
      - Marin County (Box 28)
        - Ker House (Box 28)
        - Tamalpais House (Box 28)
        - Dettner House (Box 28)
    - Cambridge, MA (Box 28)
      - Various (Box 28)
      - Churches (Box 28)
        - Christ Church (Box 28)
      - Government Buildings (Box 28)
      - Houses-Apartments (Box 28)
      - Houses (Box 28)
        - Various (Box 28)
        - Cooper Austin (Box 28)
        - A.C. Koch House (Box 30)
        - Longfellow House (Box 30)
        - Elwood (Lowell House) (Box 30)
        - Stoughton House (Box 30)
        - Wadsworth House (Box 30)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 30)
      - Libraries (Box 30)
      - Schools (Box 30)
      - Stations (Box 30)
        - Various (Box 30)
        - Harvard University (Box 30)
          - General (Box 30)
          - Buildings (Box 30)
          - Appleton Chapel (Box 30)
          - Austin Hall (Box 30)
          - Business School Building (Box 31)
          - Carpenter Center for the Visual Arts (Box 31)
          - Fogg Art Museum (Box 31)
          - Gore Hall (Box 31)
          - Graduate Center (Box 31)
          - Gymnasium (Box 31)
          - Old Harvard Hall (Box 31)
          - William James Hall (Box 31)
          - Lamont Library (Box 31)
          - Lawrence Scientific (Box 31)
          - Memorial Hall (Box 31)
          - Sever Hall (Box 31)
          - Standish Hall (Box 31)
          - University Hall (Box 31)
        - M.I.T. (Box 31)
          - Various (Box 31)
          - Auditorium (Box 31)
          - Chapel (Box 31)
          - Dormitory by A. Alto (Box 31)
    - Camden, NJ (Box 32)
    - Camden, SC (Box 32)
    - Camp Hill, PA (Box 32)
    - Camps Park, NY (Box 32)
    - Canandaigua, NY (Box 32)
    - Candor, NY (Box 32)
    - Canterbury, CT (Box 32)
    - Carlisle, PA (Box 32)
    - Carlisle, IN (Box 32)
    - Carmel, CA (Box 32)
    - Carlisle, PA (Box 32)
    - Carnasie, NY (Box 32)
    - Castleton, VT (Box 32)
    - Catskill Mountain House, NY (Box 32)
    - Cave Creek, AZ (Box 32)
    - Cazenovia, NY (Box 32)
    - Cedar Rapids, IA (Box 32)
    - Central City, CO (Box 32)
    - Centrallia, IL (Box 32)
    - Chandler, AZ (Box 32)
    - Chapel Hill, NC (Box 32)
    - Charleston, SC (Box 32)
      - Various (Box 32)
      - Churches (Box 32)
        - Various (Box 32)
        - S. Phillip's Church (Box 32)
        - S. Michael's Church (Box 32)
        - S. Paul's Church (Box 33)
      - Gates (Box 33)
      - Government Buildings (Box 33)
        - Various (Box 33)
        - County Court (Box 33)
        - City Hall (Box 33)
      - Hotels (Box 33)
      - Houses (Box 33)
        - Various (Box 33)
        - Drayton Hall (Box 33)
        - Government Thomas Bennet's House (Box 33)
        - Brewton House (Box 33)
        - Gibbes House (Box 33)
        - Heyward Washington House (Box 33)
        - Manigualt House (Box 33)
        - Russel House (Box 33)
        - Stuart House (Box 33)
        - Tradd St. Houses (Box 33)
      - Schools (Box 34)
    - Charlottesville, VA (Box 34)
      - Houses (Box 34)
        - Monticello (Box 34)
      - Jefferson Manuscripts (Box 34)
      - Plans (Box 34)
      - Exteriors (Box 34)
      - Outbuildings & Terraces (Box 34)
      - Interiors (Box 34)
      - Schools (Box 34)
        - University of Virginia (Box 34)
          - General Views (Box 34)
          - Arcades & Colonades (Box 34)
          - Gardens & Walls (Box 34)
          - Pavilions (Box 34)
          - Rotunda (Library) (Box 35)
    - Charlestown, Ma (Box 35)
    - Chelsea, M (Box 35)
    - Cherry Point, NC (Box 35)
    - Cheshire, CT (Box 35)
    - Chester, PA (Box 35)
    - Chestnut Hill, MA (Box 35)
    - Chestnut Hill, PA (Box 35)
      - Houses (Box 35)
        - Various (Box 35)
        - Esherick House (Box 35)
        - High Hollow (Box 35)
        - G. Howe House (Box 35)
        - Potter House (Box 35)
        - Venturi House (Box 35)
        - White Residence (Box 35)
    - Cheyenne, WY (Box 35)
    - Chicago, IL (Box 35)
      - Various (Box 35)
      - General Planning (Box 36)
        - Various (Box 36)
        - Proposed Civic Center (Box 36)
      - Banks (Box 36)
      - Churches (Box 36)
        - Ashe Ma'Ariv Synagogue (Box 36)
        - Jefferson Park Church (Box 36)
        - S. Mary's Church (Box 36)
        - Third Unitarian Church (Box 36)
        - Isaiah Temple (Box 36)
      - Clubs (Box 36)
        - Athletic Club (Box 36)
        - Elk's Memorial (Box 36)
        - Masonic Temple (Box 36)
        - Standard Club (Box 36)
        - West Chicago Club House (Box 36)
        - Woman's Temple (Box 36)
      - Exhibitions Halls (Box 36)
        - McCormick Place (Box 36)
      - Expositions (Box 36)
        - World's Columbian Expo, 1893 (Box 36)
          - Various (Box 36–37)
          - Administration Building (Box 37)
          - Agricultural Building (Box 37)
          - Electricity Building (Box 37)
          - Ferris wheel (Box 37)
          - Fine Arts Building (Box 37)
          - Fisheries Building (Box 37)
          - Horticultural Hall (Box 37)
          - Manufactures & liberal Arts (Box 37)
          - Machinery Building (Box 37)
          - Pristyle & Grand Basin (Box 37)
          - Southern Colonnade (Box 37)
          - Transportation Building (Box 38)
          - Women's Building (Box 38)
        - Century of Progress (Box 38)
          - Studies & Models (Box 38)
          - Plans & General (Box 38)
          - Administration Building (Box 38)
          - Agricultural Building (Box 38)
          - Amusement Building (Box 38)
          - Chrysler Motors Building (Box 38)
          - Electrical Group (Box 38)
          - Federal Building (Box 38)
          - Ford Building (Box 38)
          - Fort Dearborn (Box 38)
          - Hall of Religion (Box 38)
          - Hall of Science (Box 38)
          - Horticultural Hall (Box 38)
          - Home Exhibits (Box 38)
          - Illinois Host Building (Box 38)
          - Italian Building (Box 38)
          - Social Science Hall (Box 38)
          - Travel & Transport Building (Box 38)
      - Government Building (Box 39)
        - Second Court House (Box 39)
      - Hotels (Box 39)
        - Auditorium Hotel (Box 39)
        - Blackstone Hotel (Box 39)
        - Congress Hotel (Box 39)
        - Grand Pacific Hotel (Box 39)
        - Great Northern Hotel (Box 39)
        - Shoreland Hotel (Box 39)
      - Houses & Apartments (Box 39)
        - Various (Box 39)
        - Algoquin Apartments (Box 39)
        - Commonwealth Promenade Apartments (Box 39)
        - Francisco Apartments (Box 39)
        - Lake Shore Apartments (Box 39)
        - Marx Apartments (Box 39)
        - Promontory Apartments (Box 39)
      - Houses-Residences (Box 39)
        - Various (Box 39)
        - Bach House (Box 39)
        - Blossom House (Box 39)
        - Charnley House (Box 39)
        - Crystal House (Box 39)
        - Evans House (Box 40)
        - Farwell House (Box 40)
        - Glessner House (Box 40)
        - Harlan House (Box 40)
        - Joseph Husser House (Box 40)
        - McCormick House (Box 40)
        - McCormick House (Box 40)
        - Robie House (Box 40)
        - Roloson House (Box 40)
      - Industrial Buildings (Box 40)
        - International Leather & Belting Corporation (Box 40)
      - Libraries (Box 40)
      - Museums (Box 40)
        - Art Institute (Box 40)
        - Field Museum (Box 40)
        - Museum of Science & Industry (Box 40)
      - Office Buildings (Box 40)
        - Various (Box 40)
        - 333 N. Michigan Avenue (Box 40)
        - American Express (Box 40)
        - Bailey Building (Box 40)
        - Board of Trade (Box 40)
        - Brook Building (Box 40)
        - Cable Building (Box 40)
        - Chamber of Commerce (Box 40)
        - Champlain Building (Box 40)
        - Civic Center (Box 40)